So here's the tough cookies that a lot of us don't want to acknowledge.
There's a lot of folks that say two things can be true at one time.
But that's part of the problem.
We have reached an inflection point where no, we can't have it both ways.
You can't at the same time say this is a really good thing because I enjoyed myself,
even though it's couched in a really bad thing.
You can't say this country has the right to exist while it is simultaneously preventing an entire people from existing.
You can't say all presidents are terrible except for Obama.
So we're going to have to make hard decisions.
We're going to have to lose things.
We're going to have to understand that making a choice and taking a hard stance is the actual win.
But, you know, we don't want to do that.
I have my own versions of these as well.
However, when I see this whole like, but we can have, no, we can't.
And the sooner that we can, at least those of us who want to save the earth,
those of us who want to dismantle the Zionist Jesuit entities that are running it,
at some point, we're going to have to make hard communal choices that not everybody's going to be happy about.
So I want you to ask yourself, what is something that you have played both sides of?
And I just want you to be honest with yourself.
Like, I can say that for me, I have absolutely played both sides of entertainment content.
Like, I know that Disney and Netflix and all these places are terrible.
So, and then I'm also like, yeah, but and or, and I am getting closer and closer to that hard line.
Because the real reality of things is in my goddamn face.
And the lie that we'll tell ourselves is, well, I mean, I'm just one person.
I mean, it's like, if I don't do it, just if I don't do it, like, what does it matter?
It should matter just to you.
That hard line has to matter simply to you.
And the hard line is not a horizon.
It's hypocrisy, which I do not get down with.